<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mental Snapp</string>
    <string name="queued_exercises">Queued Exercises</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="report_an_issue">Technical support</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="login_message_1">Mental Snapp is a video diary service for people actively managing their mental health.
We believe in the power of film to change outcomes Try it for yourself - record your own story.</string>
    <string name="email">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="email_small">Email</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email_msg">Enter your Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_hint">\u2022\u2022\u2022\u2022\u2022\u2022\u2022\u2022</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="login_message_2">Do not have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="email_not_valid_text">Please enter valid email</string>
    <string name="password_not_valid_text">Enter password</string>
    <string name="email_empty">Enter email</string>
    <string name="enter_your_first_name_msg">Enter your first name</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email_add_msg">Enter your email address</string>
    <string name="enter_your_phone_msg">Enter your Phone number (Optional)</string>
    <string name="enter_your_dob_msg">Enter your Date of birth (Optional)</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone (Optional)</string>
    <string name="dob">Date of Birth (Optional)</string>
    <string name="i_am">I AM (Optional)</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="already_have_account_msg">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Username should be alphabets and numbers only</string>
    <string name="password_length_error">Password should contain minimum 6 characters</string>
    <string name="password_alphanumeric_error">Password should be alphanumeric</string>
    <string name="name_incorrect_error">Name should be alphanumeric</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_number">Please enter valid phone</string>
    <string name="enter_new_password">Please enter new password</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_password">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="enter_confirm_new_password">Please enter confirm new password</string>
    <string name="enter_confirm_password">Please enter confirm password</string>
    <string name="password_dont_match">Password and confirm password fields don\'t match</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="delete_profile">DELETE PROFILE</string>
    <string name="current_password">Current password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New password</string>
    <string name="reenter_new_password">Re-Enter new password</string>
    <string name="enter_current_password">Please enter current password</string>
    <string name="reenter_password_dont_match">Re-Enter new password does not match with new password</string>
    <string name="password_successful">Password changed successfully</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_message_1">Enter your email address below and we\'ll send you your password</string>
    <string name="reenter_password">Re-Enter password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_message_2">Enter your new password received in the email</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_title">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="go_to_email">Forgot password link has been sent to your email</string>
    <string name="issue_title">Add your title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="write_your_text">Write your text</string>
    <string name="attach_image">Attach image</string>
    <string name="enter_description">Please enter description</string>
    <string name="enter_title">Please enter title</string>
    <string name="sent_successfully">Sent successfully</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_dob">Please enter Date of birth</string>
    <string name="sign_up_successful_message">A confirmation link has been sent to your email.</string>
    <string name="password_invalid_message">Password should contain alphanumeric characters</string>
    <string name="minimum_password_length_message">Password should contain minimum 6 characters</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="no_internet">You have lost your network connection, please check your connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="successfully_updated">Successfully updated</string>
    <string name="change_screenshot">Change screenshot</string>
    <string name="accept_tnc_message_1">I accept to the</string>
    <string name="accept_tnc_message_2">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_message1"><b>Terms and Conditions</b></string>
    <string name="terms_message2">Last updated: January 03, 2017</string>
    <string name="terms_message3"><![CDATA[PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (\"TERMS\" ) CAREFULLY BEFORE
    USING THE MENTAL SNAPP MOBILE APPLICATION (THE \"APP\") OPERATED BY  MENTAL SNAPP LTD, WITH COMPANY
    NUMBER 09649971, HAVING ITS  REGISTERED OFFICE AT 101 BRAMSHOT AVENUE, LONDON, ENGLAND, SE7 7HX
    (\"US\", \"WE\", \“OUR\" OR \“MENTAL SNAPP\”).\n\nYOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE APP IS CONDITIONAL ON
    YOUR  ACCEPTANCE OF AND COMPLIANCE WITH THESE TERMS, OUR PRIVACY POLICY  AND OUR COOKIES POLICY. THESE TERMS APPLY TO
    ALL VISITORS, USERS AND  OTHERS WHO ACCESS OR USE THE APP.\n\nBY DOWNLOADING AND INSTALLING THE APP ON YOUR DEVICE YOU
    AGREE TO  BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS. IF YOU DISAGREE WITH ANY PART OF THE TERMS  THEN YOU MAY NOT ACCESS THE APP.]]></string>
    <string name="terms_message4"><b>IMPORTANT NOTICE</b>: The App permits you to record information relating to your mental
        health. We do not, and the App is not intended to be used, to offer any medical or other  healthcare advice to you.\n\n
        <b>ABOUT THE APP</b>\n\nThe key features of the App include:\n\n\u2022 The ability to post, link, store, share and
        otherwise make available certain  information, text, graphics, videos, or other material relating to your mental
        health  (“Content”);\n\n\u2022 Rating your Content according to mood and graphs produced over time of  variations
        in mood as well as usage of the App; and\n\n\u2022 Respond to guided exercises that are designed to support you to gain
        insight into  your mental health.</string>
    <string name="terms_message5"><b>REGISTRATION</b> Once you have downloaded the App, you must register an account to access
        and use the App by completing the online registration form on the App (“Account”).\n\nYou may not use as a username
        the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject
        to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorisation, or a name that is otherwise
        offensive, vulgar or obscene.\n\nUpon the completion and submission of the online registration form on the App, you
        shall be sent a verification email (“Verification Email”) to the email address you provided on the registration form.
        This Verification Email will contain details of how to activate your Account. Your Account will not be accessible until
        you have accepted these Terms.\n\nYou shall keep your registration details for the App (“Login Details”) confidential
        and secure. Without prejudice to any other rights and remedies available to you, we reserve the right to promptly disable
        your Login Details and suspend your access to the App in the event that we have any reason to believe you have breached
        any part of these Terms.\n\nNotwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to:\n\n\u2022 accept or reject your application to
        register for any reason; and\n\n\u2022 suspend your Account and/or refuse you access to the App (partly or wholly) if you breach
        any of the provisions hereunder.\n\nYou agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us
        immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorised use of your Account.\n\nYou hereby warrant that
        the information provided by you to us is true, accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes
        a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your Account.</string>
    <string name="terms_message6"><b>ACCESSING THE APP</b>\nSubject to these Terms, we hereby grant to you a non-exclusive,
        non-transferable (without  a right to sub-licence) and terminable licence to access the App. This licence is in
        respect  of your use of the App for your own personal, non-commercial purposes only.\n\nExcept as expressly permitted
        in these Terms, you shall not, and shall not permit others to  (i) modify, translate, create derivative copies of or
        copy the App, in whole or in part; (ii)  reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or otherwise reduce the object
        code of the App  to source code form; (iii) distribute, sub-licence, assign, share, timeshare, sell, rent, lease,
        grant a security interest in, use for service bureau purposes, or otherwise transfer the App  or your right to use the
        App; (iv) remove or modify any copyright, trademark, or other  proprietary notices belonging to Us or our licensors
        contained within the App; or (v) use  the App in any manner not expressly authorised by these Terms.\n\nWe will use our
        reasonable endeavours to make the App available to you at all times, but  we cannot guarantee that the App will be
        uninterrupted or fault free. Routine and essential  maintenance and upgrades may be required from time to time to improve,
        add functions or  restore the App.\n\nWe may suspend your access to the App and/or terminate your Account, wholly or
        partly,  at any time without notice to you if any of the following events occur:\n\n\u2022 Our third party service and
        network providers cease to make the third party services  or network available to us;\n\n\u2022 We are undertaking repairs
        , planned maintenance or upgrades to the App;\n\n\u2022 We believe that you or someone using your login details has failed
        to comply with  one or more of these Terms;\n\n\u2022 We believe that there has been fraudulent use, misuse or abuse of
        features or  functionalities of the App (in whole or in part);\n\n\u2022 We believe that you have provided us with any
        false, inaccurate or misleading  information; and\n\n\u2022 We believe that you are not acting in a personal capacity.</string>
    <string name="terms_message7"><b>YOUR OBLIGATIONS</b>\nYou shall, at all times:\n\n\u2022 Comply with all applicable
        laws, regulations, directives and legislations in your use  of the App;\n\n\u2022 Ensure that the device you use to
        access the App complies with any minimum  specification released by us from time to time and required for your device to
        use all  the features and functionality of the App and contains adequate anti-virus protection  and you acknowledge that we
        will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by a  virus or other technologically harmful material that may infect your
        device due to  your use of the App, and you hereby release and discharge us from any liability for  such loss or damage;\n\n
        \u2022 Comply with any guidelines provided or reasonable instructions issued by us from  time to time in respect of your use
        of the App;\n\n\u2022 Not do anything likely to impair, interfere with or damage or cause harm or distress  to any persons
        using the App;\n\n\u2022 Not use the App and/or any knowledge, information, know-how and/or expertise  derived from using
        the App to commit any criminal act; and\n\n\u2022 Not use the App and/or do anything that shall or be reasonably deemed to
        infringe  any intellectual property rights or other rights of any third parties.\n\nIn addition to the obligations above,
        you shall not submit to appear on the App any  information (including any data, comments, images, videos, third party URL
        links or other  material whatsoever in any format) that may reasonably be deemed to be offensive, illegal,  inappropriate or
        that in any way:\n\n\u2022 Promotes racism, bigotry, hatred or physical harm of any kind against any group or  individual;\n\n
        \u2022 Harasses or advocates harassment of another person;\n\n\u2022 Displays pornographic or sexually explicit material;\n\n
        \u2022 Promotes any conduct that is abusive, threatening, obscene, defamatory or  libelous;\n\n\u2022 Promotes any illegal
        activities;\n\n\u2022 Provides instructional information about illegal activities, including violating  someone else’s privacy
        or providing or creating computer viruses;\n\n\u2022 Promotes or contains information that you know or believe to be inaccurate,
        false or  misleading;\n\n\u2022 May be deemed to be a misrepresentation of any facts;\n\n\u2022 Engages in or promote
        commercial activities and/or sales, including but not limited  to contests, sweepstakes, barter, advertising and pyramid
        schemes, without our  prior written consent; or\n\n\u2022 Infringes any rights of any third party including but not limited
        to intellectual property  rights.\n\nWhen you upload Content, you give to Mental Snapp Ltd a worldwide, non-exclusive,
        royalty-free, transferable licence (with right to sub-licence) to use, reproduce, distribute  and display that Content in
        connection with the provision of the App. We also reserve the  right to remove any Content displayed on the App at any time
        and without notice at our  sole discretion.\n\nUnless otherwise explicitly stated by us, we do not vet, verify the accuracy,
        correctness  and completeness any of your Content created, submitted and/or provided by you through  the App or otherwise to
        determine whether it may result in any liability to any third party.  You hereby warrant that you have the rights to use all
        such information, data and material  in the manner set out in these Terms. WE EXPRESSLY EXCLUDE OUR LIABILITY FOR  ANY LOSS OR
        DAMAGE ARISING FROM THE USE OF OUR APP BY YOU IN  CONTRAVENTION OF THIS SECTION (YOUR OBLIGATIONS).\n\nIn the event that we,
        in our sole and absolute discretion, consider that you have breached  any of these Terms, we reserve the right to take any
        action that we deem to be necessary,  including without limitation, disabling your login details, suspending your use of
        and  access to the App; and in the case of illegal use, the instigation of legal proceedings  and/or disclosure of such
        information to law enforcement authorities or third parties as we  reasonably feel is necessary.\n\n<b>APP-STORES</b>\n
        You acknowledge and agree that:\n\n\u2022 We are in no way linked, connected or affiliated with Apple, Google, Microsoft
        or  any other app-store provider;\n\n\u2022 Access to and use of the App may be limited by your network carrier and will
        be  limited if you are attempting to access the App from outside the United Kingdom;\n\n\u2022 You acknowledge you will not
        be able to access and use certain functionalities of  the App unless You have internet access through a GPRS, 3G, 4G or
        Wi-Fi  connected device. All traffic charges or access charges incurred due to the use of  the App are subject to your
        agreed terms with your network provider;\n\n\u2022 Neither your airtime provider nor any app-store or app-store operator
        (including but  not limited to the “App-Store” or “Google Play” store) shall bear any  responsibility or liability
        whatsoever in relation to sale, distribution, functionality,  accessibility, performance or non-performance of the App;\n\n
        \u2022 Your airtime provider and any app-store or app-store operator (including but not  limited to the “App-Store” or
        “Google Play” store) are third party beneficiaries in respect of  this clause and accordingly have the right to enforce the provisions
        of this clause;\n\n\u2022 We are solely responsible for providing any support and maintenance in respect of  the App; and\n\n
        \u2022 You will comply with any third party terms and conditions which may be applicable  from time to time in relation to
        your use of the App.\n\nFurther, where you have obtained the App from the Android ‘Google Play’ store, you acknowledge  and agree that:\n\n
        \u2022 You are not located in a country that is subject to a US Government embargo or  that has been designated by the US
        Government as a ‘terrorist supporting’ country;\n\n\u2022 You are not listed on any US Government list of prohibited or
        restricted parties;\n\n\u2022 These Terms are concluded between you and us and accordingly Android is not a  party to these
        Terms;\n\n\u2022 Android has no obligation to provide any maintenance and support services in respect  of the App;\n\n\u2022 If
        the App fails to conform to any warranty herein, you may notify Android following  which Android will refund you the purchase
        price paid for the App (if any). Android will  have no further liability whatsoever in respect of any such failure;\n\n
        \u2022 Android has no responsibility to address any claims by you or any third party  whatsoever with respect to the App;\n\n
        \u2022 Android shall not be responsible for any claims made by any third party that the App  infringes any third party intellectual
        property rights; and\n\n\u2022 \'Google Play’ and ‘Android’ are trade marks of Android Inc.\n\n<b>INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</b>\nOther
        than in relation to any links to third party websites and your Content, we own or have  a licence to use all right,
        title and interest in and to the App, including without limitation all  copyright and any other intellectual property
        rights therein. These Terms shall not be  construed to convey title to or ownership of the App or the content
        contained therein to  you. All rights in and to the App or content not expressly granted to you are reserved by  us.\n\n
        You are expressly prohibited from removing, modifying, altering or using any registered or  unregistered marks/logos
        owned by us, and doing anything which may be seen to take  unfair advantage of our reputation and goodwill or could be
        considered an infringement of  any of the intellectual property rights owned and/or licensed to us, without first
        obtaining  our written permission.\n\n<b>TERMINATION</b>\n\nYour ability to access and use the App shall continue
        until terminated in accordance with  these Terms.\n\nWe may terminate or suspend your Account immediately, without
        prior notice or liability,  for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach any part of these
        Terms.\n\nYou may terminate your Account at any time by notifying us in writing by email, requesting  that your Account
        is terminated.\n\nOn termination of your use of the App in accordance with these Terms:\n\n\u2022 You will no longer be
        entitled to access the App; and\n\n\u2022 Unless otherwise revoked by us, your access to the App will be limited for the
        purpose of downloading video Content which you have submitted to the App prior to termination. This limited access
        shall be available to you for a period of 30 days from the date that your Account is terminated. Thereafter, all Content
        that you have submitted and/or made available to the App shall be removed.\n\n\u2022 Mental Snapp is committed to returning all
        video Content that you have submitted and/or made available to the App. Without prejudice to any of our rights in these
        Terms, if requested by you, we hereby agree to remove all Content that you have submitted to the App (only to the extent
        that we are not bound by any existing law and legislation to retain such Content).\n\n<b>WARRANTIES AND LIABILITY</b>\n
        Links to third party websites and companies may appear on the App. We accept no responsibility for the availability,
        suitability, reliability or content of such third party websites and do not necessarily endorse the views expressed
        within them.\n\n<b>We are responsible to you for foreseeable loss and damage caused by us.</b> If we fail to comply with
        these Terms, we are responsible for loss or damage you suffer that is a foreseeable result of our breaking these Terms
        or our failing to use reasonable care and skill, but we are not responsible for any loss or damage that is not
        foreseeable. Loss or damage is foreseeable if either it is obvious that it will happen or if, at the time you accepted
        these Terms, both we and you knew it might happen.\n\n<b>We do not exclude or limit in any way our liability to you where
        it would be unlawful to do so.</b> This includes liability for death or personal injury caused by our negligence or the
         negligence of our employees, agents or subcontractors or for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation.\n\n<b>Our maximum aggregate
        liability to you.</b> If you suffer loss or damage that is a foreseeable result of our breaching these Terms, our failing
        to use reasonable care and skill or otherwise, the maximum amount you may claim from us shall be one hundred pounds
        sterling (£100.00).\n\n<b>When we are liable for damage to your property.</b> If defective digital content that we
        have supplied damages a device or digital content belonging to you, we will either repair the damage or pay you
        compensation. However, we will not be liable for damage that you could have avoided by following our advice to apply
        an update offered to you or for damage that was caused by you failing to correctly follow installation instructions or to
        have in place the minimum system requirements advised by us.\n\n<b>We are not liable for business losses.</b> The App
        is for domestic and private use. If you use the App for any commercial, business or resale purpose we will have no
        liability to you for any loss of profit, loss of business, business interruption, or loss of business opportunity.\n\n
        <b>Please back-up content and data used with the App.</b> We recommend that you back up any Content used in connection
        with the App, to protect yourself in case of problems with the App.\n\n<b>Check that the App is suitable for you.</b>
        The App has not been developed to meet your individual requirements. Please check that the facilities and functions of
        the App (as described on the relevant app-store site) meet your requirements.\n\n<b>We are not responsible for events outside
        our control.</b> If our provision of the App or support for the App is delayed by an event outside our control then we
        will contact you as soon as possible to let you know and we will take steps to minimise the effect of the delay. Provided
        we do this we will not be liable for delays caused by the event.\n\n<b>Your use of the App is at your sole risk.</b> The
        App is provided on an \"AS IS\" and \"AS AVAILABLE\" basis. All content, information and material provided
        to you as part of the App does not constitute advice or a recommendation and therefore it should not be solely relied
        on to assist in making or refraining from making a decision, or to assist in deciding on a course of action. We shall
        not be responsible in any way for any advice which may be provided to you based on your Content. The App is provided
        without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability
        , fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.\n\n<b>You must be 18 or over to accept these Terms
         and use the App</b>\nYou must be 18 or over to accept these Terms and use the App.\n\n<b>You may not transfer the App to
            someone else</b>\nWe are giving you personally the right to use the App. You may not transfer the App to someone
        else, whether for money, for anything else or for free. If you sell any device on which the App is installed, you must
        remove the App from it.\n\n<b>Changes to these Terms</b>\nWe may need to change these Terms to reflect changes in law
        or best practice or to deal with additional features which we introduce.\n\nWe will give you notice of any change by
        notifying you of a change when you next start the App or by e-mail. By continuing to use the App after such alteration,
        you will be deemed to have accepted any amendment to these Terms.\n\n<b>Updates to the App</b>\nFrom time to time we
        may automatically update the App to improve performance, enhance functionality, reflect changes to the operating system
        or address security issues. Alternatively we may ask you to update the App for these reasons.\n\nIf you choose not to install
        such updates or if you opt out of automatic updates you may not be able to continue using the App.\n\n<b>If someone else
            owns the phone or device you are using</b>\nIf you download the App onto any phone or other device not owned by you, you
        must have the owner’s permission to do so. You will be responsible for complying with these Terms, whether or not you own
        the phone or other device.\n\n<b>WE MAY TRANSFER TO SOMEONE ELSE</b>\nWe may transfer our rights and obligations under
        these Terms to another organisation. We will always tell you in writing if this happens and we will ensure that the
        transfer will not affect your rights under these Terms.\n\n<b>YOU NEED OUR CONSENT TO TRANSFER YOUR RIGHTS TO SOMEONE
        ELSE</b>\nYou may only transfer your rights or your obligations under these Terms to another person if we agree in
        writing.\n\n<b>NO RIGHTS FOR THIRD PARTIES</b>\nThese Terms do not give rise to any rights under the Contracts (Rights
        of Third Parties) Act 1999 to enforce any part of these Terms.\n\n<b>IF A COURT FINDS PART OF THESE TERMS ILLEGAL, THE
        REST WILL CONTINUE IN FORCE</b>\n Each of the paragraphs of these Terms operates separately. If any court or
        relevant authority decides that any of them are illegal, unlawful or otherwise unenforceable, the remaining paragraphs
        will remain in full force and effect.\n\n<b>EVEN IF WE DELAY IN ENFORCING THESE TERMS, WE CAN STILL ENFORCE IT LATER</b>\n
        Even if we delay in enforcing these Terms, we can still enforce it later. If we do not insist immediately that you do
        anything you are required to do under these Terms, or if we delay in taking steps against you in respect of your breaking
        these Terms, that will not mean that you do not have to do those things and it will not prevent us taking steps against you
        at a later date.\n\n<b>WHICH LAWS APPLY TO THESE TERMS AND WHERE YOU MAY BRING LEGAL PROCEEDINGS</b>\nThese Terms are governed
        by English law and you can bring legal proceedings in respect of the App in the English courts.\n\n<b>PRIVACY POLICY</b>\nWe will
        only use your Personal Information (as defined in our Privacy Policy) in accordance with our Privacy Policy.\n\n You agree that
        our Privacy Policy constitutes part of these Terms. You must read our Privacy Policy before you use the App.\n\n<b>CONTACT
        US</b>\nIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us by email at feedback@mentalsnapp.com, by telephone
        on 08009708363 or by post at Mental Snapp Ltd, 101 Bramshot Avenue,\nLondon, SE7 7HX.</string>
    <string name="tnc_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="check_tnc_message">Please agree to Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_message1"><b>Privacy Policy</b></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_message2">Last updated: January 03, 2017</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_message3">Mental Snapp Ltd (\"us\", \"we\", or \"our\") operates the
        Mental Snapp mobile application (the \"App\").\n\nThis page informs you of our policies regarding the
        collection, use and disclosure of Personal  Information when you use our App.\n\nWe will not use or share your
        information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\n\nWe use your Personal Information for providing
        and improving the App. By using the App, you  agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this
        policy. Unless otherwise  defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as
        in our  terms and conditions.\n\nBy using the App, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with
        this policy.\n\n<b>How Do We Collect Your Information?</b>\n\nWhile using our App, we may collect certain personally
        identifiable information that can be used to  contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include,
        but is not limited to:\n\n\u2022 Name;\n\u2022 Video Content relating to mental health;\n\u2022 Contact information such as email addresses
        and telephone numbers; and\n\u2022 Demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests\n\n(together \"Personal Information\").\n\nWhen you access the App by or through a mobile device, we may also collect certain information
        automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device  unique ID, the IP
        address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile  Internet browser you use and other
        statistics.\n\n<b>How Do We Use Your Information?</b>\n\nWe use your Personal Information for providing and improving
        the App. This includes:\n\n\u2022 Providing and managing your Account;\n\u2022 Providing and managing your access to the App;\n\u2022 Personalising
        and tailoring your experience when accessing the App;\n\u2022 Responding to communications from you;\n\u2022 Market research; and\n
        \u2022 Analysing your use of the App and gathering feedback to enable us to continually improve the App  and your user experience.\n\n
        With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your Personal Information  for marketing purposes which
        may include contacting you with newsletters, marketing or  promotional materials and other information that may be of interest
        to you. You may opt out of  receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or
        instructions provided in any email we send.\n\n<b>How and Where Do We Store Your Information?</b>\nThe data that we collect
        from you will not be transferred to, or stored at, a destination outside the  European Economic Area (EEA). However, data
        collected may be processed by staff operating  outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. These staff may
        be engaged in the  fulfilment of your request, order or reservation and the provision of support services. We will take
        all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with  this Privacy Policy.\n\n
        We only keep your Personal Information for as long as we need to in order to use it as described  above, and/or for as long
        as we have your permission to keep it.\n\nIt is important to remember that the transmission of information via the internet
        may not be  completely secure and that you are advised to take suitable precautions when transmitting to us  information via
        the internet.\n\nIf your personal details change, you may update them by accessing the App. If you have any  questions about
        how we use information collected which relates to you, please contact us using the  contact details provided below.\n\n<b>Who
        Do We Transfer Your Information To?</b>\nWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our App, to
        provide the App on  our behalf, to perform App-related services or to assist us in analysing how our App is used. These
        third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and  are obligated not to
        disclose or use it for any other purpose.\n\nWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or
        in accordance with an  order of a court of competent jurisdiction, or if we believe that such action is necessary to
        comply  with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of  our App.\n\n
        If Mental Snapp Ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information  may be transferred. We
        will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and  becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. In
        the event of such a transfer of information, your  rights under the Data Protection Act 1998 are not affected.\n\nIn the
        event that a dispute arises with regards to the international transfer of data, you agree that the  courts of England and
        Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction over the matter.\n\n<b>How Do I Access My Information/Data?</b>\nThe Data Protection
        Act 1998 (\"Act\") gives you the right to access information that we may hold  about you. Any access request will be processed
        by us within a reasonable amount of time.\n\nAny access request will be subject to a fee of £5 to meet our costs in providing
        you with details of  the information we hold about you.\n\n<b>Will the App Contain Links to Third Party Websites?</b>\nWe
        do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but our App may  contain links to other sites
        that are not operated by us. We use these third party links to support and  enhance your experience of the App.\n\nYou should
        note that clicking on a third party link may direct you to that third party\'s site. We  strongly advise you to review the
        privacy policy of every site you visit. We have no control over,  and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies
        or practices of any third party sites or  services.\n\n<b>Do We Collect Personal Information From Children?</b>\nOur App
        does not address anyone under the age of 18.\n\nWe do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone
        under 18. If you are a  parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information,
        please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from anyone  under the age of 18 without
        verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that  information from our servers.\n\n<b>Changes to This
        Privacy Policy</b>\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting
        the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for  any changes. Changes
        to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.\n\nIf we make any material changes to this Privacy
        Policy, you will be notified either through the  email address you have provided us, by placing a prominent notice on our
        App, or by displaying the  new privacy policy on-screen which you may be required to read and accept in order to continue
        your use of the App.\n\n<b>Jurisdiction</b>\nThis Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of
        England and Wales,  without regard to its conflict of law provisions.\n\n<b>Contact Us</b>\nIf you have any questions
        about these Terms, please contact us by email at  feedback@mentalsnapp.com, by telephone on 08009708363 or by post at
        Mental Snapp Ltd, 101  Bramshot Avenue, London, SE7 7HX.\n\nPlease ensure that your query is clear, particularly if it is a
        request for information about the  Personal Information we hold about you.</string>
    <string name="invalid_credentials_message">Invalid credentials</string>
    <string name="exercise_title">Exercise</string>
    <string name="videos_title">Videos</string>
    <string name="insights_title">Insights</string>
    <string name="record_title">Record</string>


    <string name="text_photo_library">Photo Library</string>
    <string name="text_take_photo">Take Photo</string>
    <string name="text_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="text_delete_photo">Delete Photo</string>
    <string name="add_video_name">Add video name</string>
    <string name="add_tags">Add tags with #</string>
    <string name="add_feelings">Add Feeling</string>
    <string name="add_feeling_description_hint">What\'s going on? you can write about it here. You can also use hashtags(like #happy or #tired).</string>
    <string name="best_mood_capital">THE BEST</string>
    <string name="very_good_mood_capital">VERY GOOD</string>
    <string name="good_mood_capital">GOOD</string>
    <string name="ok_mood_capital">OK</string>
    <string name="bad_mood_capital">BAD</string>
    <string name="very_bad_mood_capital">VERY BAD</string>
    <string name="worst_mood_capital">THE WORST</string>
    <string name="best_mood">The Best</string>
    <string name="very_good_mood">Very Good</string>
    <string name="good_mood">Good</string>
    <string name="ok_mood">Ok</string>
    <string name="bad_mood">Bad</string>
    <string name="very_bad_mood">Very Bad</string>
    <string name="worst_mood">The Worst</string>
    <string name="set_mood_title">Set mood</string>

    <string name="picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="description_info">Info</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="feelings_title">Feelings</string>
    <string name="select_mood">Please select a mood</string>
    <string name="select_feeling">Please select a feeling</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="no_videos_to_show">No videos to show</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="alert_message_camera">You can record videos that are up to 2 minutes long.</string>
    <string name="signup_logo_message">Record your own story</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="video_downloaded">You have successfully downloaded the video</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="all_video_downloaded">All videos downloaded successfully</string>
    <string name="goodbye_message">Thank you for using Mentalsnapp. We\'re sorry to see you go. Hope you enjoyed telling your story and meet you again soon.</string>
    <string name="schedule_time_error">Scheduling time should be minimum 10 minutes ahead from present time</string>
    <string name="schedule_message">You have exercise scheduled for:</string>
    <string name="bar_chart_loading_message">No data available</string>
    <string name="schedule_delete_message">Successfully removed</string>
    <string name="email_feedback">feedback@mentalsnapp.com</string>
    <string name="feedback_subject">: Feedback for mentalsnapp android app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title">How to use</string>
    <string name="record_onboard_title">Video Recording Guides</string>
    <string name="enjoy_telling_your_story">Enjoy telling your story</string>
    <string name="enter_your_last_name_msg">Enter your last name</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>

    <string-array name="onboarding_titles">
        <item>Welcome!</item>
        <item>How it works</item>
        <item>Exercises</item>
        <item>Exercise questions</item>
        <item>Mood rating</item>
        <item>Insights</item>
        <item>My videos</item>
        <item>Your data</item>
        <item>Deleting and downloading</item>
        <item>Your profile</item>
        <item>One last thing</item>
        <item>Tap to start immediately</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="onboarding_description">
        <item>Mental Snapp is a new video diary service for people actively managing their mental health.\n\n
            The purpose of recording video diaries with Mental Snapp is to make your voice and awareness of your mental health useful to you. We
            believe that you already have the skills to manage your mental health successfully, and creating video diaries on a
            regular basis can draw out the expertise you have already.</item>
        <item>We encourage you to record freeform or in your own words as much as possible so it becomes part and parcel of your
            routine. You can set regular times to record, whenever the time is right for you.\n\nWe recognise this may take a bit of
            getting used to! We’ve created some optional prompts to help you through the first few videos.</item>
        <item>You might have days when you can’t think of what you want to say, don’t worry, we’ve come up with some guided exercises
            to help you through.\n\nThe guided exercises are split into the following sections:\nEveryday coping\nWellbeing\n
            Purpose\nRelationships\nSOS</item>
        <item>After you have selected an exercise category and subcategory, the individual exercises come up as single questions.
            You can swipe right to select the question you want to answer.\nYou then press record now - or if you would rather -
            schedule the exercise for later using the calendar icon.\nYou can see your queued exercises on the ‘More’ tab.</item>
        <item>After recording, then you rate your mood, from ‘the best’ to ‘the worst’ or grades in between using the wheel. You
            then give the video a feeling - these are taken from Plutchik, a recognised system of emotional categories.\n\nYou
            also have the option to add your own free text as tags. These ratings and tags will form an overview of how you are
            doing so you can track your feelings and emotions.</item>
        <item>Over time you will be able to track your mood and gain insight on your mental health. In doing so, you will be
            able to take control again. You can review the videos any time.\n\nSingle click on a point on the graph to show
            the tags and name of the video - double click on a point to play the video.</item>
        <item>You can search the videos by date, exercise category, feeling or any of the freeform text you have entered against
            them.\n\nYou can play the videos and share them with others - but only if you show them yourself on your phone.\n\nThat
            way you can get an immediate response and you know they’ve been seen.</item>
        <item>Your data is important to us so we have put policies in place to protect it. We are compliant with the Information
            Commissioners Office.\n\nWe make our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy available on our website as well as in
            the app here.</item>
        <item>Your data remains yours, and you can download the videos at any time.\nYou also have the right to delete your data
            when you delete the app.\n\nWe wouldn’t want our time together to be cut short, but if you did want to leave we aim
            to make it easy for you.</item>
        <item>You can customise your profile to make it useful to you.\n\nYou might want to set a reminder to record Mental Snapp, daily, every
            few days, or weekly. It’s up to you.</item>
        <item>Sometimes recording a diary is boring, sometimes it’s a chore. It’s an everyday thing, part of the routine.In the poem
            Born Yesterday, Phillip Larkin reflects on what it is to be ordinary. The poem ends;\n\n\"… may you be dull -\nIf that
            is what a skilled,\nVigilant, flexible,\nUnemphasised, enthralled\nCatching of happiness is called.\"</item>
        <item>Tap here for our guide to recording your first videos</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="record_title_array">
        <item>Say hello</item>
        <item>How did that feel?</item>
        <item>What’s your response?</item>
        <item>Your stats</item>
        <item>Who are you speaking to?</item>
        <item>Congratulations!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="record_description_array">
        <item>This is your first video diary. Say hello to yourself, to Mental Snapp, introduce yourself, see how it feels. Then
            rate your mood, tag it with feelings, upload. Well done.</item>
        <item>When you’re ready, it’s time to record again. How did making that first recording feel? Was it what you were
            expecting? Is there anything that surprised you? Rate your mood again, tag the feelings, and you’re done.</item>
        <item>Have you watched yourself back yet? Take some time to watch one or both of the recordings that you’ve made, in
            preparation to make another one. How does it feel watching yourself back? Have you learnt anything? Any surprises?
            Tag and upload. Well done.</item>
        <item>You’re building up a picture of your current state. Look at your stats page, and record a response. Do they seem
            to reflect where you are at the moment? What would you add or take away? Tell the story of how you were then, and
            how you are today.</item>
        <item>You’re building a relationship with yourself as if you were a friend, seeing yourself from the outside. Does this
            feel like a new way to relate to yourself? What are you learning? Who are you speaking to when you record your own
            story? Rate your mood, tag your feelings.</item>
        <item>You’ve reached the end of this guide, but are at the very beginning of your journey to record your own story. In
            a total of 10 short minutes, you have rated your mood and logged your story 5 times. That process encourages ‘
            metacognition’ - thinking about thinking - which is a skill that will stand you in good stead in the future. Well
            done. Keep going.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
